Cengage Group Privacy Overview
==============================

Simply put, your privacy is our priority.
-----------------------------------------

We know you use Cengage Group products and services to learn—to build the knowledge, skills and confidence you need to succeed. You can trust that Cengage Group will always handle your personal information respectfully and responsibly so that you can interact with us in confidence.

All Cengage Group companies are bound by our Global Privacy Program, which protects the personal information we receive from you as well as information we receive from schools and other third parties. It protects information collected online as well as offline. 

Additional Privacy Program Information
--------------------------------------

[Privacy Statement Regarding K-12 Students and Children’s Data](https://www.cengagegroup.com/privacy/k12-notice/)

[Important Information for Residents of the People’s Republic of China](https://www.cengage.com/privacy/important-information-for-residents-of-the-people%E2%80%99s-republic-of-china)

[Important Information for Residents of the EEA, Switzerland and the UK](https://www.cengagegroup.com/privacy/important-information-for-residents-eea-switzerland-uk/)

Important Information for Residents of Canada
---------------------------------------------

Our collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information is done on the basis of your consent (implied or express) or where otherwise permitted or required by the laws of Canada, including the laws of the applicable province. You imply your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information as described in the [Cengage Group Privacy Notice](https://www.cengagegroup.com/privacy/notice/) where you provide your Personal Information to us or use our Services and have access to the [Cengage Group Privacy Notice](https://www.cengagegroup.com/privacy/notice/) or as described in any other privacy notice that you may be given when your Personal Information is collected. We will process any request from you to access, correct or delete your Personal Information under the appropriate Canadian law.

Privacy Statement for Hosted School Websites
--------------------------------------------

Certain Cengage Group businesses, like Ed2Go, administer websites that provide course materials and services for educational institutions and companies. Information collected on these websites is only used by us to support our clients and provide the services requested by the course instructors. We do not use this information for our own purposes. Most educational institution student course records are also protected by the Family and Educational Rights Privacy Act (FERPA). For information on your company or school's privacy policies, please contact your school’s administration.

Our hosted websites may offer students and professionals the opportunity to interact directly with Cengage Learning. If so, the [Cengage Group Privacy Notice](https://www.cengagegroup.com/privacy/notice/) will apply to that information.

Social Security Number Policy Statement
---------------------------------------

Cengage Learning, Inc. and its affiliates collect U.S. Social Security numbers and other sensitive Personal Information in the ordinary course of its business. We have implemented reasonable technical, physical and administrative safeguards to help protect sensitive Personal Information from unlawful use and unauthorized disclosure. All Cengage Group workers are required to follow these established safeguards, which include the following:

* Access to sensitive Personal Information is limited to those workers and service providers who have a need to access the information to perform tasks for Cengage Group. Sensitive Personal Information is only disclosed to third parties in accordance with Cengage Group's established privacy and security policies.
* Cengage Group will only disclose sensitive Personal Information (1) to those service providers, auditors, advisors and/or successors in interest who are legally or contractually obligated to protect them, or (2) as required or permitted by law.

If you have any questions, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.cengage.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).
